So now that we know how to create data block using this software, next we are going to see how to edit
or how to update a sector trailer or the key A or key B.
So to update key A or key B, it's quite simple.
You just need to know the sector number or the sector trailer number in each sector.
So if you want to update sector eight, sector nine or whatever sector you want to update, let's suppose
you want to update.
Let's just go a little down and let's just suppose you want to update.
Sector 13 and in sector 13, the sector trailer block is 55.
Right.
So you have to remember that.
In Sector 13, The sector trailer block is 55.
You can see it over here and you can enter 55 over here.
And this tool reads decimal to decimal, right?
So you don't need to update decimal to hex, right?
Like we were doing in ACR 1 to 2 as before.
So we were updating this address address block into hexadecimal.
So we were converting this address block in hexadecimal first, and then we were entering into ACR 1
to 2 Usdc.
But over here, this software accepts decimal number, so you just need to enter the decimal number.
So let's just first read the data on 55 block.
All right.
So as you can see, it's a sector trailer block.
And we know this by knowing the key B and the excess bits over here.
And we also know that the first key A is not visible, right?
So it's not readable in any case.
So it's a sector trailer block Now, if you want to update a sector trailer block, all you have to
do is you have to enter data.
Similarly where we enter the data for updating the data.
Block right?
So we have to enter the same data or the data which we want to update over the same data transmission.
Block Right.
So let's just do it so we will not enter 000 because as we know, key is not visible, but we have to
enter the correct key, right?
So it's six time F.
So let me enter it over here.
And make sure you use caps lock, because this software only works in capital letters.
So.
Right.
Four time.
Five time.
And the sixth time.
So it's key.
Now we have to enter the axis beds, which are these four beds.
So it's starting from F.
Zero seven.
Eight zero.
Six.
Nine.
Right.
And then f, f, f, f, f, f and f f, Right.
So this is the structure of transportation mode.
So we are just going to, you know, first do in the transportation mode and we will not change the
keys just to check.
Right?
So let's just do data, right?
So as you can see, data is written successfully.
Let's just read this data.
And we are able to read the data same as it is we were reading before because we haven't changed anything
in our keys, Right.
So let's just update key A so we will change the first two bytes of key A.
So we have updated the key a the first two bytes and let's just do data right?
And data is written successfully.
Now, let's just try to read this data.
And over here you can see authentication falling.
That means we are not able to read data.
Right?
And this is the case because we haven't changed the key over here, because each time when we do any
operation, we first have to authenticate.
So each time we first authenticate, then whatever operation we want to do, either we have to update,
delete any data or change the access bit.
All all the things.
First we have to do is authenticate with key A or key B, and that depends on the access bits, right?
So we are in a transportation mode right now, but we have changed the key.
So let's just update the keys over here and we will authenticate with the new key.
And do read data.
And now we are able to read data, but we are not able to read Key A and I have told you the reason
we are not able to read Key A in any case, whether we change the access bits, there are certain cases
in which key B is also not readable and access bits are not readable.
You can see all those conditions in the access bits table, which we have discussed before.
So we have updated and you can see the result.
Now let's just update key B as well.
So we will update KB over here.
We'll change the first two bits of KB as well.
First two bytes.
And let's just do data, right?
So data is written successfully and let's just do data read again.
And over here you can see the.
Kibby is changed and Kibbee is because visible we can change.
C The visible change in the log description over here, right?
So this is how you change and modify sector trailer.
Just need to remember the sector number and then you can modify the sector block as well.
In the next video, we are going to see how to modify value blocks and how to do increment and decrement
operation on value blocks.